{
    "subject": "resource/Niantic,_Inc.",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/Ingress_(video_game)",
    "human_readable": "Niantic, Inc. produces Ingress.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5859094262123108,
            "question": "What company produced the game Ingress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5828325152397156,
            "question": "Does Niantic, Inc. produce other types of software besides games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44678062200546265,
            "question": "Name a game developed by Niantic, Inc."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4381958842277527,
            "question": "What is Ingress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3861127197742462,
            "question": "Is Niantic, Inc. known for developing mobile games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36730659008026123,
            "question": "Who created the game Ingress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30355051159858704,
            "question": "What are some popular features of Ingress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22625517845153809,
            "question": "How has Ingress impacted the gaming industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.222209632396698,
            "question": "What type of game is Ingress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18494060635566711,
            "question": "What makes Ingress unique compared to other games?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Niantic, Inc. produces Ingress.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2556_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of game is Ingress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2556_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Ingress impacted the gaming industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2556_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular features of Ingress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2556_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2556_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Niantic, Inc., including its production of games such as Ingress. Therefore, the statement \"Niantic, Inc. produces Ingress\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}